The next area I want to talk about is one that I'm particular proud of myself, pretty much designed this under my own thinking.
What we have here, is what I'm going to call the small head target mirrors.
I've got four foot square mirrors adjusted a little bit different heights on the wall here.
And, what I have my boxers do is pick one that is approximately their face is dead center of that mirror.
What we do is, is I tell them if you take a step back from the mirror.
As you punch yourself in the face, you can simulate that being another boxer punching you.
So, as you step forward and your fist comes almost directly into your face you can expect that other boxer to be punching you.
So, what we're trying to do is get your face out of the target out of the head target mirror.
Ok.
So, as we're stepping forward we're going to bend at the knees and get our face out of the mirror. Ok. Our first, on the other hand is still going directly into mirror directly into their face.
They don't train at Bill's gym so you can bet that their face is going to still be here, while your face is down a little bit lower and out of the head target mirror.
When you step back again, it's ok to have your face in the mirror.
They can't hit you, you can't hit them.
You're half a step away, this is where you need to relax.
So, as we step forward we're bending down.
We're getting out of the mirror.
Ok. And, not only is that good for just a jab. But, it is also good as you can see for the one two left right.
Ok. We start throwing now one two, two rights. Again, keep your face out of the mirror. So, four different height mirrors for four different boxers.
Even this one here, for the younger boxers.
Actually, I had to draw a little circle in the mirror.
Because, they were so small that they were covering the whole mirror.
So, again it's one of the few times where being having your face directly in the mirror is not a good thing.
Thanks.